jzool.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Jzool.com and our sellers know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting Jzool.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

  * What Personal Information About Customers Does Jzool.com Gather?
  * About Cookies
  * Does Jzool.com Share the Information It Receives?
  * How Secure Is Information About Me?
  * Examples of Information Collected

### What personal information about customers does Jzool.com gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Jzool.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * #### Information you give us

We receive and store any information you enter on our site or give us in any other way (examples).  We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 

  * #### Automatically acquired information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Jzool.com. (See here for examples) 

  * #### E-mail communications

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Jzool.com. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your profile settings accordingly. 

  * #### Information from Other Sources

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. (See here for examples) 

### About Cookies?

Cookies are clusters of alphanumeric data that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to make things easy for you when you return to our site. No personal information is stored in our cookies but we do keep information such as your language settings and also the items you stored in your shopping cart until your next visit. 

Most browsers will give you the option to disable cookies, however we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to use our Shopping Cart, Checkout or Purchasing features, other features on Jzool.com which require you to Sign in. 

### Does Jzool.com Share the Information It Receives?

We care about your privacy and we will never sell or disclose your information to third parties except in the cases described below. 

  * #### Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control

We work closely with our affiliated businesses such as our sellers. These businesses operate stores at Jzool.com or sell offerings to you at Jzool.com. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when a seller or third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party. 

  * #### Third-Party Service Providers

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, translating product descritptions, providing customer service, and processing credit card payments. These third-parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

  * #### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice. Also, in the unlikely event that Jzool.com, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

  * #### Protection of Jzool.com and Others

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Jzool.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation this privacy policy. 

  * #### With Your Consent

In cases other than the above, you will receive notice when information is to be released to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

### How secure is my information?

We do our best to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

However, it is still to protect your password to prevent unauthorized access. 

### Examples of information collected

  * #### Information You Give Us

You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product;  provide information in your account or your profile; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile wish lists or other gift registries;  participate in other community features; provide and rate reviews; and share information with friends. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number. **However, please note that we do not retain any credit card information** on our system. 

  * #### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include your ip address; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and timezone setting, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the url clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call customer support. 

  * #### Information from Other Sources

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties; search terms and search result information. 

  * #### Information You Can Access

Examples of information you can access at Jzool.com include your order history and profile information.
